http://www.tdwilliamson.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Important SHORTSTOPP® II Plugging Machine Customer Notification. Click to read more.
SOLUTIONS
Integrated Pigging Integrated Pigging PigsPigging System ComponentsPigging Services Pipeline Integrity Pipeline Integrity In-line InspectionNon-Destructive EvaluationIntegrity Engineering Solutions Intervention & Isolation Intervention & Isolation Tapping MachinesPlugging MachinesValves & FittingsServices
What's the best way to maintain optimal product flow in your pipeline and maximize return on your investment? Tell us your challenges and we’ll help you find the solutions.
Find Your Solution
RESOURCES
Product Bulletins Product Bulletins Case Studies Case Studies Papers Papers Videos Videos News News Training Training
What's the best way to maintain optimal product flow in your pipeline and maximize return on your investment? Tell us your challenges and we’ll help you find the solutions.
Find Your Solution
COMPANY
Who We Are Who We Are History Careers Careers Company Culture QHSE QHSE Events Events Community Relations Community Relations
What's the best way to maintain optimal product flow in your pipeline and maximize return on your investment? Tell us your challenges and we’ll help you find the solutions.
Find Your Solution
CONTACT
What's the best way to maintain optimal product flow in your pipeline and maximize return on your investment? Tell us your challenges and we’ll help you find the solutions.
Find Your Solution
Search
Select LanguageEnglishEspañolFrançais
Privacy Policy1. About UsT.D. Williamson, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, the "Company", "we" or "us") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through compliance with this Privacy Policy (this "Policy"). When you visit tdwilliamson.com (the "Website"), this Policy governs the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide and our practices for collecting, using and disclosing that information. More information on the entities involved is in Section 4 below.This Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by the Company or any third party.Please review this Policy carefully before using any part of the Website."Personal data" is understood to mean all information which relates to an identified or identifiable natural person, whereby a natural person is considered to be "identifiable" in this context when that person can be identified directly or indirectly, especially by means of attributing a designation such as a name, an identification number, location data or an online designation or one or more special characteristics which are an expression of the physical, physiological, genetic, psychological, economic, cultural or other social identity of this natural person.As data controller, we respect your right to privacy and will only process your personal information in accordance with applicable data protection laws and as described in this Policy.We may revise and update this Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. It is your responsibility to regularly check for updates to this Policy. We will try to inform you of any change if reasonably possible. If you do not agree with this Policy, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Website.2. Data ProcessingBelow you will find an overview of:The categories of personal data that we use and store about you;The purposes for which this information would be collected;The legal basis for processing. Categories of Personal DataPurpose(s) for ProcessingLegal Basis for Processing1Your personal contact details including your full name, gender, home and work address, landline and mobile phone numbers, e-mail addressesAnswer to your request in accordance with the functionality “submit my request”To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.This processing may be based on the performance of the contract between us or on your consent, depending on the nature of your requestThis processing may be based on the performance of the contract between us or on your consent, depending on the nature of your requestThis processing may be based on the performance of the contract between us or on your consent, depending on the nature of your requestTo enable us to display advertisements to our targetYour consent or our legitimate interest which is to advertise our activitiesTo communicate with youThis processing may be based on the performance of the contract between us or on your consent, depending on the nature of your request2This processing may be based on the performance of the contract between us or on your consent, depending on the nature of your requestWebsite personalization, convenience, statistical purposes that help us design, administer and improve the WebsiteTo allow you to participate in interactive features and functionality on the WebsiteOur legitimate interest to improve our website and interact with you.3Information related to your preferences, your interest and other personal informationTo provide you with information, products or services that you request from usTo market products and services which we think may be of interest to youYour consent3. Children Under the Age of 16The Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any information to us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on the Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including, without limitation, your name, address, online contact information (including email address), telephone number, persistent identifiers that can be used to recognize a user over time and across different websites or online services, geolocation information or any other personally identifiable information. If we learn we have collected or received personally identifiable information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us.4. Disclosure of Your Information4.1. PrincipleWe will not disclose your personal data to any third party, except as described in this Policy.Communicating via the Internet and sending information, products and services to you by other means necessarily involves your personally identifiable information passing through or being handled by third-parties, but we do not sell or distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties forpurposes of allowing them to market their products and services to you without your consent.4.2. ExceptionsWe may disclose aggregated and non-personally identifiable information about our users without restriction.We may disclose personally identifiable information that we collect or you provide as follows:To our subsidiaries and affiliates, including around the world which may involve transfer from countries within the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries outside the EEA.To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.Also, we employ agents to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders,deliveries,sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments and providing customer support. Those agents have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personally identifiable information held by us about our Website users is among the assets transferred.To third parties to market their products or services, in accordance with your consent.To fulfill the purpose for which you specify.For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information with your consent.We may also disclose your personally identifiable information for the following additional reasons:To comply with any court order, law or other legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company, our customers or others.We are not responsible for personal information you provide to other websites.Be aware that the Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites, which are not affiliated with or under the control of the Company. Any information that you may submit through such other websites is not subject this Policy. We encourage you to review the Policy of each other website you visit.5. Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologyWe may use cookies, web beacons or other similar tracking technologies. These are used to assist with your navigation of the Website and may also be used for advertising purposes. You can erase or block these tracking technologies, although it may impair your full functionality of the Website.6. SecurityWe take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide to us against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental destruction, loss or damage.7. Data RetentionYour personal Information is stored by us and/or our service providers, strictly to the extent necessary for the performance of our obligations and strictly for the time necessary to achieve the purposes for which the information is collected, in accordance with applicable data protection laws.When we no longer need to use your information, we will remove it from our systems and records and/or take steps to properly anonymise it so that you can no longer be identified from it (unless we need to keep your information to comply with legal or regulatory obligations to which we are subject). This means that, if you no longer have a live and valid entitlement to TDW services and you have not logged into our service for 5 years then we will take steps to delete or anonymise your personal information.We will not store your personal data to send you marketing emails for more than 3 years after the end of our commercial relationship with you.8. Your RightsYou have the following rights as a data subject:You may "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional messages from us by following the instructions in those messages,The right to access to personal information that we hold about you,The right to ask us to update or correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you,The right to erasure where the conditions of article 17 of the GDPR have been met,The right to restriction of processing where the conditions of article 18 of the GDPR have been met,The right to data portability insofar the conditions of article 20 GDPR apply to you,The right to give us instructions on the management of your data after your death,The right to object to processing of personal data concerning you, insofar the conditions under article 21 GDPR have been met,The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.If you need help or wish to exercise any of the above rights or have questions about them, please contact us using the details hereinafter.We will consider all such requests and provide our response as soon as we can. Please note, however, that personal information may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances, which may include needing to keep processing your personal information for our legitimate interests or to comply with a legal obligation. Please note that we may request you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity.To exercise these rights, please refer to section 9 below.9. Contact UsIf you have any complaints, queries or questions about how we use your personal information, you may contact us using the contact details set out below. We will then get in touch with you to see how we can help.If you have a complaint about how we use your personal information, we would always prefer you to contact us first. However, you may also make a complaint to the relevant data privacy regulator if you wish to do so. Please let us know if you are unsure about how to get in touch with the data privacy regulatorIf you need to contact us or have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at: Dataprivacy@tdwilliamson.comIf you have any questions about the Website, please contact:T.D. Williamson,Inc. Attention: Website Manager6120 South Yale, Suite 1700Tulsa, Oklahoma 74136United States of AmericaThank you for visiting the Website.
TOP
